to switch back to the old way that your
iPhone looked before you upgraded to iOS
26. And if this video helps you, please
consider giving it a like and also
subscribe to my channel because that
really helps me out. So, if you don't
like the look of liquid glass where the
different menus and things are
transparent and that makes it a little
harder to see what you're doing, there
is no way to turn off liquid glass, but
there are some settings changes we can
make to make it easier to see and reduce
the transparency. So to do that, open up
the settings on your iPhone. Then just
scroll down to the second section and
select accessibility. Once in there,
select display and text size. And then
all you want to do is select reduce
transparency. Now you can go back to
your home screen. And when you open up a
folder, as you can see, there is no
transparent liquid glass look.
Additionally, if you find that the menu
buttons on your home screen or the icons
are a little hard to see, we can change
the look of that by simply holding down
on a blank area of your home screen and
then selecting edit in the top left.
From there, select customize. And you
just want to choose either dark and
that'll make it darker or you can choose
tinted and change the colors there. So,
if you want it to be a little bit
darker, depending on your needs, you can
choose different colors and make it dark
there so that it is easier for you to
see on that liquid glass background. So,